mylivetv.net 2016-11-01

# MyLiveTV :: Privacy Policy

MyLiveTVM  is a firm believer in upholding the privacy of the users and members of its affiliated websites. To lend credence to our intentions, we have formulated this elaborate privacy policy which sets forth our concerns. By accessing this website, you acknowledge and fully understand MyLiveTVM 's Privacy Policy and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this website Privacy Policy. 

## Participating third parties' policies

The websites accessible through the

##  third party links

on this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed on the respective websites. Since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of these websites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before providing any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

## Privacy of Information collected

MyLiveTVM  collects certain information from and about its users in three ways -

## Web Server Logs

When you visit our website, we may track some information to administer the site efficiently and analyze its usage so that we may provide its users with the best possible service. Examples of information we may track includes: 

  * The Internet Protocol (IP) address,
  * The browser or computer you use,
  * Number of links clicked within the site,
  * State or country from which the site is accessed,
  * Date and time of the visit,
  * Name of the Internet Service Provider (ISP),
  * Web page you linked to our site from,
  * Pages viewed on the site.

## Cookies and Web beacons

MyLiveTVM  may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Some cookies may be considered harmful for privacy but it is our endeavor to deposit cookies that are absolutely safe and secure from any privacy breach. Cookies are uniquely assigned to every user, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to such user. The sole purpose of our cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save your time. MyLiveTVM  reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partners and affiliates, but does not allow the third parties to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into [www.google.com](http://www.google.com/), [www.worldpay.com](http://www.worldpay.com/) sites that relies on third-party cookies).

The web pages on this site may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (or 'clear GIFs' or 'single-pixel gifs') â€“ that allow MyLiveTVM  to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. MyLiveTVM  may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. 

## Personal Information of Users/Members

When the users register themselves to avail of different features offered by [www.mylive.tv](http://www.mylive.tv/), we collect certain personal information, including users' address, phone number, e-mail address, phone, fax etc. This is in continuation of our endeavor to provide you with better services offered through this website. Any financial information provided by you during the course of transactions with the website, is kept confidential and if the credit card information is sought for trading purposes, this information is forwarded to your credit card provider and not to any third party. 

Any personal information collected by [www.mylive.tv](http://www.mylive.tv/) will be kept secret and confidential and will not be disclosed under any circumstances, except â€“

  * to facilitate your service request;
  * to respond to legal processes or to comply with the law;
  * to protect ourselves from liability; or
  * in connection with a merger, acquisition or liquidation of the company.

## Publicly shared personal information

We can do our best to keep your personal information confidential and expect the same amount of diligence from your side. You can help us in maintaining mutual trust and privacy by abstaining from sharing the personal information (user ID, password etc.) on discussion boards, forums, social networking sites etc.). 

Your user name (not your email address) is displayed to other users when you upload multimedia content or send messages through this site and other users can contact you through messages and comments sent to your user name. Any multimedia content that you submit to www.mylive.tv may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

## Privacy of children

This website is strictly meant for people above 13 years of age. If you are below 13 years of age, please cease any usage of this website immediately. If it comes to our knowledge that www.mylive.tv has inadvertently collected any personal information from a child below 13 years of age, we shall take immediate and appropriate steps to purge such information. 

## Effect of sale/merger/acquisition etc. on privacy of information

In the event of sale/merger/acquisition etc. of MyLiveTVM , we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information collected from the users/members as part of such sale/merger/acquisition. 

In an unlikely event of our bankruptcy/insolvency/reorganization/receivership/assignment for the benefit of creditors/application of laws/equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

## Updates and modifications

This Privacy Policy is subject to amendments/alterations/updates/modifications. We encourage all the users and members of this website to periodically keep themselves abreast of any such change in this Policy.

## Contacting Us

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Policy and/or our general practices, please contact us at [support@mylive.tv](mailto:support@mylive.tv) or send your comments to: 

MyLiveTV, Inc.  
Attention: Privacy Statement Personal  
Suite 105, 501 Silverside Road, Wilmington, DE 19809, USA 

MyLiveTVM  will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
